Before I start shampooing this young lady, I want to let you know that I draped her with a shampoo cape.
Nice and thick like this and put the towel over.
A nice thick towel.
I'm going to begin to shampoo her.
When we shampoo curly hair, it's even more manageable and it's easy to shampoo.
We use a hydrating shampoo.
It's something that's going to detangle and be easy to manipulate.
You want the hair to be soft and to be easy for you to comb and cut.
It also gives her a little bit of conditioning.
Curly hair tends to be a bit dry.
It's going to be a little dry because it's curly.
I'm going to go ahead and wet the hair real thoroughly and use again a hydrating shampoo for her.
A good hydrating shampoo.
Give a good 2 shampoos and make sure you go all the way down to the ends.
Scrub the hair real well and then proceed to condition after.